in a world that is constantly growing we
are always on the moon
chasing goals realizing dreams
and discovering newer joys in life
what if you could have the protection of
a trusted Health partner every step of
your way forward
whether you're home or abroad present it
Asia Lombard Health Advantage Apex plus
plan a health partner that protects you
at home or abroad it has been designed
to deliver you worldwide coverage so you
can experience enhanced Peace of Mind
confidence and freedom
the booking of offerings in this plan
includes some insured limit up to three
crores 60 days pre and 180 days post
hospitalization expenses daily
consultations coverage for all day care
treatments domestic air ambulance cover
home care cover starting with Worldwide
coverage for hospitalization you can get
protection for expenses up to the sum in
short
this benefit can be unlocked for a sum
insured of 25 lakhs and above
with the pre and post hospitalization
benefit you get covered for medical
expenses incurred for repeated up to 60
days before and 180 days after an
insured person's admission to hospital
it also offers tele consultations and
recommendations for routine health
concerns by qualified medical
practitioner giving you more and prompt
access to Wellness
further on the ambulance cover feature
includes the expenses incurred on
emergency bases for using domestic air
ambulance services
the domestic air ambulance service
coverage is up to the summon shot
medical expenses incurred by in short
for daycare treatments as an inpatient
in a hospital for less than 24 hours are
also covered Home Care treatment expense
is also covered for a customer who opt
to get treated at the comfort of their
homes provided it is prescribed by the
doctor too apart from these enhanced
features the new Health Advantage plan
comes with a host of other benefits that
ensure robust coverage so give your
health care the advantage it deserves
with unci Lombard Health Advantage Apex
plus black